I'm holding 7 pounds
and inside them there is 1 Golden Bell
in case you find any of them
scattered around the city you will win 1 jersey
just like that you don't get 1 calm pants there
pera there leaves EU
EU never
I made bet
I tried hard to be the way she did
who said they need us imagine the bro will
take a roll in the city
type hunting tribe
to find Charlie Brown's packaging
bro said time matters to us
I was happy when we were alone she told me that
fear of success is on the seal of Dora who said they
who said they need
glue it to the stall no it can
if you find the golden bell
just stick it here in the stall
the weeping brother bar
that you will pick up your t-shirt with us
Charlie Brown Junior officer
the games start now you think it got good
one more the hunt
starts now I think it got good is
from the time we go there
see if got that shirt
opened right up to the cell phone man
make the crowd run
behind envelope around town is an activation
wider is on
but i need to create some idea to
activate points of sale
bro and that's what i need to do from now on
found stuck there
generated let's go away then
I want to see these guys find this golden gray now
valid until tomorrow